<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Hawaii State Senate Districts 2022</title>
                <onlink>https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services/AdminBnd/MapServer/34</onlink>
                <onlink>https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/senate22.pdf</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>[Metadata] 2022 Hawaii State Senate District Boundaries as adopted by the State of Hawaii Reapportionment Commission in 2022. Source: Hawaii State Office of Elections, March 2022.Please note - if you download the data from the State's 
geoportal (https://geoportal.hawaii.gov/), the data is exported in WGS84
 coordinates, although it is stored internally (in the State's 
geodatabase), served in the State's web services 
(https://geodata.hawaii.gov/arcgis/rest/services), and made available in
 the State's legacy download site 
(https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis/download-gis-data-expanded/) in UTM/NAD
 83 HARN coordinates.For additional information, please refer to metadata at https://files.hawaii.gov/dbedt/op/gis/data/senate22.pdf or contact Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov; Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</abstract>
            <purpose>Hawaii State Senate Districts 2022</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>legislative districts</themekey>
                <themekey>congressional districts</themekey>
                <themekey>house districts</themekey>
                <themekey>senate districts</themekey>
                <themekey>elections</themekey>
                <themekey>voting</themekey>
                <themekey>reapportionment</themekey>
                <themekey>hawaii</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>Other Constraints</accconst>
        <useconst>State of Hawaii Terms of Use. 



The
 contents of this web page are public domain and to the extent indicated
 otherwise in the Terms of Use, are exempt from Terms of Use policy 
restrictions.There are no expressed warranties associated with the 
release of this data or product. Specifically, no warranty is made that 
the GIS data or any subsequent updates will be error free and no 
warranty is made regarding the positional or thematic accuracy of the 
GIS data. The GIS data and any features depicted do not represent or 
confer any legal rights, privileges, benefits, boundaries or claims of 
any kind. The Office of Planning and Sustainable Development encourages users to report any 
discrepancies or errors found. 
 Contact: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program, Office of Planning and 
Sustainable Development, State of Hawaii; PO Box 2359, Honolulu, Hi. 
96804; (808) 587-2846; email: gis@hawaii.gov. Website: https://planning.hawaii.gov/gis.</useconst>
        <datacred>Hawaii State Office of Elections; Hawaii Statewide GIS Program</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20220412</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
